https://www.careeronestop.org/Site/site-privacy.aspx

Skip to content
your source for career exploration, training & jobs
Sponsored by the U.S. Department of Labor.
A proud partner of the
network.
your source for career exploration, training & jobs
Sponsored by the U.S. Department of Labor.
A proud partner of the
network.
your source for career exploration, training & jobsEspañolKeywordsMenu
Explore Careers
What kind of career will fit you best? How can you get there? Read More...Self assessmentsWhat is an assessment?Interest assessmentSkills assessmentWork valuesLearn about careersCareer ClustersCareer profilesCareer videosWhat's hotCompare occupationsResearch industriesPlan your careerSet career goalsSalariesLicensed occupationsProfessional development
Occupation Profile
Get wages, employment trends, skills needed, and more for any occupation.
Occupation Profile
Occupation
Location
Career Tools
Target Occupation
Salary Finder
Skills Matcher
Compare Occupations
Green Careers
Find Training
Find the education and training resources you need. Read More...Types of trainingHigh school equivalencyAdult Basic EducationShort-term trainingCollegeCertificationsApprenticeshipsInternshipsProfessional developmentDo you need a license?Pay for trainingHow much will it cost?Find money for trainingFinancial aidScholarshipsMake a budgetFind your pathWhat's right for me?What's in demand?Make a training planMy skills are out of dateCollege for adultsIs education worth it?
Find Local Training
Find training programs, colleges, and universities in your local area.
Find Local Training
Occupation, school, or program
Location
Education and Training Tools
Certification Finder
License Finder
Scholarship Finder
Professional Associations
Job Search
Taking the time to make a job search plan will pay off for that next job. Read More...Plan your job searchCreate a job search planResearch employersResearch salariesOnline job searchWhat's in demand?Inquiry lettersInquiry letters sampleNetworkingWhy network?Your elevator speechMake a list of contactsInformational interviewsContact potential employersMaintain your networkTake your network onlineFind jobsWhat are job banks?State job banksEmployment agenciesFederal employmentMilitary optionsJob fairsResumes and applicationsResumesCover lettersCover letters sampleJob applicationsOnline applicationsPortfoliosWork samplesReferencesInterview and negotiateGet interview readyTypes of interviewsInterview tipsCommon interview questionsThank-you notesNegotiate your salaryIs this offer right?Job search tipsNot getting results?Background checksAre you overqualifiedRelocateYour online imageJob search checklist
Find a Job Now
Search for jobs in any location across the United States.
Find a Job Now
Job?
Where?
Job Tools
Business Finder
Veterans Job Matcher
Resume Guide
Find a Job Club
Salary Finder
Find Local Help
Find workforce services in your neighborhood or across the country.
Read More...American Job CentersFind American Job CentersEmployment and training programsApprenticeship Office FinderEmployment Network FinderFarmworker Jobs Program FinderJob Corps Center FinderNative American Program FinderOlder Worker Program FinderRefugee Assistance FinderWIOA-Eligible Training Program FinderYouth Program FinderCommunity servicesCommunity College FinderJob Club FinderLibrary FinderMaps To State ServicesState ProfilesState Web DirectoryWorkforce developmentWorkforce Development Board FinderYouth Committee FinderUnemployment benefitsUnemployment Benefits Finder
Find an American Job Center
American Job Centers can help you look for work and offer job search workshops, free computer access, and more.
Find an American Job Center
Location
Toolkit
Find the tools you need to research career information, training, or jobs. Read More...CareersInterest AssessmentOccupation ProfileWork Values MatcherTarget OccupationsCompare OccupationsGreen CareersFastest-GrowingMost OpeningsLargest EmploymentDeclining EmploymentCompare Employment TrendsTrainingLocal Training FinderCertification FinderScholarship FinderLicense FinderProfessional Association FinderSkillsSkills MatchermySkills myFutureTools & Technology FinderJobsJob FinderVeterans Job MatcherBusiness FinderResume GuideWagesCompare SalariesSalary FinderHighest-Paying CareersIndustryEmployment PatternsFastest-Growing IndustriesHighest-Paying IndustriesIndustries with Declining EmploymentIndustries with Largest EmploymentState and LocalAvailable WorkforceState ProfilesLabor Market InformationSee Local Help
Resources For
Find career, training and job search resources just for you. Read More...Getting Back to WorkGetting Back to WorkCareer changerCareer changerMilitary and veteransMilitary and veteransWorker with a criminal convictionWorker with a criminal convictionEntry-level workerEntry-level workerOlder workerOlder workerYoung adultYoung adultWorkers with disabilitiesWorkers with disabilitiesBusinessesBusinessCareer advisorsCareer advisorSelf-employmentSelf-employmentCredential seekerCredential seeker
Search by Keyword
Search CareerOneStop
Site Privacy
Print
Email
Babel
Share on Facebook
Share on Twitter
Share on LinkedIn
Tell us where to send a link to this page.
Email the page
To
Receiver's email address, use comma to separate addresses
From
Your email address
Send Email
Cancel
Sending...
Your email has been sent. Thank you.
Site Privacy
Privacy policy for CareerOneStop websites
Thank you for visiting one of the CareerOneStop sites, which include the Credentials Center, the Business Center, GetMyFuture, Job Search Help for Ex-Offenders, mySkills myFuture, Worker ReEmployment, Veteran and Military Transition Center, Disaster Recovery Services, America’s Service Locator, and America's Career InfoNet.
Our privacy policy is clear: we will collect no personal information about you when you visit any of our websites unless you choose to provide that information to us, nor will we share that information with any other party except as discussed below.
Information collected and stored automatically
While you browse through our website, read pages, or download information, we gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store the following information about visits made to our website:
The IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which our website is accessed;
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site
The date and time our site is accessed
The pages visited
If a CareerOneStop website is visited from another website, the address of that website
We aggregate this information and use it to help us make our site more useful to visitors -- to learn about the number of visitors to our site, to determine those portions of our site which are of greatest interest to our users, and to learn about the types of technology our visitors use.
Use of cookies
CareerOneStop websites use cookies to measure website activity. Cookies are small amounts of information stored on your computer by your web browser software. None of the information collected is personally identifiable. CareerOneStop, America’s Career InfoNet, America’s Service Locator and mySkills myFuture websites use both single session temporary cookies and multi-session persistent cookies for the purpose of website measurement.
Single session cookies are temporarily stored on your computer and are deleted as soon as you close your web browser. Multi-session cookies are used for the purpose of web measurement, and to improve your online experience by remembering your online interactions and preferences across multiple sessions, and identify if you are a returning user. None of the information stored in either single session or multi-session cookies used by CareerOneStop contain any personally identifiable information. Information collected for web measurement is stored and maintained indefinitely for the purpose of historical web measurement and tracking.
If you prefer not to have non-personally identifiable persistent multi-session cookies stored on your computer you can opt out. Doing so will not affect your use of our site, nor restrict your access to any site content or resources. Click here to opt-out of multi-session usage tracking.
Or, you can remove or block the use of multi-session web measurement technologies by changing the settings of your browser as described at USA.gov’s web measurement and customization opt-out web page.
Information collected from emails
All e-mail information provided to America’s Career InfoNet, and America’s Service Locator (as a part of a mailing list or as feedback to our Service Center) is only used for the provided purpose. We do not share our e-mail with any other organizations, unless we are required to as part of a law enforcement investigation.
Security, intrusion, and detection issues
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this government computer system employs software programs that monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.
Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.
Links to other sites
CareerOneStop websites have links to other government agencies and private organizations. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.
Disclaimer
These websites were created to support public access to career and occupational information. The information was created and is maintained by other public and private organizations and is the responsibility of these organizations. The accuracy of the information for individual occupations is subject to error because of the many factors that affect the economy over time. While occupational projections and related job outlook information can provide valuable inputs to the career decision-making process, they should not be the sole basis of a career choice.
Further, the inclusion of links to particular items or sites is not intended to reflect their importance, nor is it intended to endorse any views expressed or products or services offered by the author of the reference or the organization operating the server on which the reference is maintained.
Privacy policy for CareerOneStop mobile applications
The privacy policy for CareerOneStop mobile applications is the same as above, expect in these specific cases:
Emails
When creating an account to use the TAP mobile application, you must provide a valid e-mail address and password. This information is stored on secure servers and is not made available to any third parties. The e-mail address is used to contact a user who has forgotten a password.
Occasionally, we use the e-mail addresses we are provided to seek comments from individuals on services offered. These comments allow us to determine how to improve our services and improve our relationship with those who use our services. You may decide to send us personally-identifying information, for example your mailing address or telephone number, in an electronic mail message requesting information. Information collected in this manner is used solely for responding to requests for information. We may forward your e-mail to other representatives of the Department of Labor or its contractors who are better able to respond to you.
Scheduled expiration of inactive user accounts
If a user has not 'logged in' or accessed an account for more than a year, the account will expire (be made inactive).
Our commitment to data security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
All user information on the TAP mobile application is maintained on a secure server. The information can only be accessed through an administrator login or through direct access to the server. User information is not shared with any third parties. We are committed to protecting users' privacy and ensuring that personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner.
Microsoft Geocoding Terms of Use
CareerOneStop Geocoding is provided through a license agreement with Microsoft. Your use of the data is subject to the Microsoft Bing Maps Terms of Service.
https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/maps/product
You may use the Geocodes locally in your applications. But, Geocodes cannot be stored, copied or shared. Please refer to the Microsoft Bing Terms of Use.
How to contact us
Questions or comments about these privacy policies? Please e-mail us at info@careeronestop.org.
Find Local HelpAmerican Job Centers
Find your nearest local office
Employment or training help:1-877-US2-JOBS
(1-877-872-5627)
TTY:1-877-889-5627CareerOneStop help:info@CareerOneStop.org
Explore & FindExplore CareersFind TrainingJob SearchFind Local HelpToolkitResources For ...Video LibraryOur SitesCareerOneStopBusiness CenterCompetency Model ClearinghouseCredentials CenterDisaster RecoveryEmployment RecoveryEx-OffendersGetMyFuturemySkills myFutureVeteransWorker ReEmploymentHelpFAQsData SourcesCite this WebsiteNeed to Register?For DevelopersLink to UsData DownloadsWeb APIWidgets and LogosNews CenterBlogOutreach MaterialsCareerOneStop NewsNews RoundUpConnect with UsFacebookTwitterLinkedInYouTubePinterestMobile AppsAlexa
For information about jobs, training, career resources, or unemployment benefits call:
1-877-US2-JOBS
(1-877-872-5627)
or TTY
1-877-889-5627
For help using the CareerOneStop website:
info@careeronestop.org
CareerOneStop is sponsored by the U.S. Department of Labor, Employment and Training Administration
CareerOneStop is sponsored by the U.S. Department of Labor, Employment and Training Administration
A proud partner of the
network.
Survey dialogTake our 3-question survey?
The survey is available in English only.
